{
    "subject": "resource/32nd_Medical_Brigade",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Medical_brigades_of_the_United_States_Army",
    "human_readable": "The 32nd Medical Brigade is about medical brigades of the United States Army.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.929840087890625,
            "question": "What branch of the military does the 32nd Medical Brigade belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9296665191650391,
            "question": "What role does the 32nd Medical Brigade play in military operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8680068850517273,
            "question": "What number designates the 32nd Medical Brigade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8430781960487366,
            "question": "Where would a 32nd Medical Brigade likely be deployed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8154527544975281,
            "question": "Are there different types of medical brigades within the US Army?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6479912400245667,
            "question": "What kind of personnel are typically found within a medical brigade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6066675186157227,
            "question": "What is the primary function of a medical brigade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6000233292579651,
            "question": "How do medical brigades contribute to the overall success of a military mission?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5057494640350342,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a task performed by a medical brigade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41542932391166687,
            "question": "What training and qualifications are required for personnel serving in a medical brigade?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The 32nd Medical Brigade is about medical brigades of the United States Army.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3845_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a task performed by a medical brigade?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3845_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How do medical brigades contribute to the overall success of a military mission?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3845_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary function of a medical brigade?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3845_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3845_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3845_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3845_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3845_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3845_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3845_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3845_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3845_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3845_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3845_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text provided describes the history, structure, and purpose of the 32nd Medical Brigade, clearly indicating its role within the United States Army's medical system.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The files provided contain detailed information about the 32nd Medical Brigade, its structure, and its role within the United States Army. This suggests that the brigade's focus is indeed on medical services and brigades of the US Army."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents contain information relevant to the operations, lineage, and nature of the 32nd Medical Brigade within the U.S. Army, which supports the statement that \"The 32nd Medical Brigade is about medical brigades of the United States Army.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}